<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-04-22T20:04:52-04:00</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Katherine and Michael’s Wedding</title><subtitle>:wedding: We're getting MARRIED!</subtitle><author><name>Katherine and Michael</name></author><entry><title type="html">We Made a Wedding Website!</title><link href="/2018/03/11/we-made-a-wedding-website.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="We Made a Wedding Website!" /><published>2018-03-11T18:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-03-11T18:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/2018/03/11/we-made-a-wedding-website</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/03/11/we-made-a-wedding-website.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;'assets/test.jpg'&quot; alt=&quot;useful image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well well well, you know it’s serious when there’s a website for it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like any great relationship, this website is a work in progress.  Feel free to poke around and check things out.  If you’d like to RSVP, just head over to &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSd_MzuuS82EDIATcF792774-Nrx1SGetv0fAx3lipBHtAOeoA/viewform?usp=sf_link&quot;&gt;this form&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s pretty much it for now, but we’ll keep the updates coming!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Katherine and Michael</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">We Made a Wedding Website!</title><link href="/2018/03/11/home_material.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="We Made a Wedding Website!" /><published>2018-03-11T18:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-03-11T18:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/2018/03/11/home_material</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/03/11/home_material.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-wedding&quot;&gt;The Wedding&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;![Granville Inn Photo]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saturday, September 1, 2018
2:30 PM
[RSVP For Wedding]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ceremony
St Edwards Catholic Church
785 Newark Granville Rd, Granville, OH 43023, USA
Reception
Granville Inn
314 East Broadway, Granville, OH 43023, USA&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please join us for a celebration of marriage at St Edwards Catholic Church at 2:30PM on September 1st.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dinner, dancing, and lots of laughter to follow at the Granville Inn&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;other-events&quot;&gt;Other Events&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome Dinner&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;![AirBnB Photo]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday, August 31, 0007
6:30 PM
Almosta Farm
2893 Mounts Road Northwest, Alexandria, OH 43001, United States&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We would love to host our guests from near and far for a welcome dinner  at Almosta Farm - an Airbnb rented by the Chamber’s family.  Dinner be served  from 6:30-7:30PM, drinks and relaxing until 9:00PM. If your travel plans will allow you to attend, please RSVP!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[RSVP for Welcome Dinner]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afternoon hangout
Somewhere fun? Almosta Farm or Buckeye Lake Winery?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;eight-year-love-saga&quot;&gt;Eight Year Love Saga&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;from-katherine&quot;&gt;From Katherine:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw Michael for the first time during my freshman year of college. He was tall, had a shock of hair that stood on end, wore orange crocs and owl sweaters, and had a huge smile. From then on, I had a crush. We were both biology majors, and I would try and catch him in the lab or leaving the Science Center on his way to the pottery studio. He was somewhat of a campus legend (ask me about it sometime…) so I didn’t think my prospects were good. However, during junior year he spotted me at church, asked a friend for my number, and invited me on a hike. I was thrilled. The evening after the hike, I received a text message from him that read “that was lovely, let’s do it again.” It was sweet, and it was straightforward. I’ve never doubted his commitment in the eight years that have followed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then, we have wandered everywhere together - both literal and metaphorical! We both pursued secondary education and maintained a long distance relationship, at times it was a “long hike relationship” as Michael pursued his dreams out West. In 2014, Michael moved to D.C. and our relationship blossomed. We have learned what it’s like to be a team, to support each other, and to choose to love every day. This September, I’m thrilled to get to publicly seal the deal with my first and only love, surrounded by our friends and family!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;from-michael&quot;&gt;FROM MICHAEL:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Awe shucks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really need ta put some good time and thought into this little diddy, but I will take this opportunity to say I’m s till gonna put season passes to Zoombezie Bay in our wedding registry!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wedding-party&quot;&gt;Wedding Party&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daniel Touzinsky - Man of Honor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daniel is Katherine’s brother, and with that comes several very important titles: chief of operations for neighborhood games, flashlight tag point person, confidant, total goofball, and longest-time friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Touzinsky - Groomsman&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James is the brides brother &amp;amp; the life of the party. His arrival in the Touzinsky household brought a lot of joy and an extended stay for Santa Claus, Gus the leprechaun, and other magical houseguests. While he doesn’t believe in them anymore, he’s 100% likely to quote memes, have great fashion (obviously) and be up on the latest dance moves&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maura Campbell - Bridesmaid&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maura is an cool, calm, and collected lady who does not shy away from the quirky (100% a requirement to be bbf’s with the bride).  She’s turned her eye for the unusual into a passion - something you’ll witness if you’re lucky enough to catch one of her video art exhibitions. She’s been a source of inspiration and silly jokes for Katherine since ‘02!
Erin McKenna - Bridesmaid&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Erin has been the bride’s friend for 20 years. They grew up on Liberty Lane and brought quite a bit of ridiculous fun to the heart of Ohio’s ‘burbs. She’s often moved to tears over beautiful colors, and lights up the world with passion, dedication, and zest everywhere she goes!
Valerie Vogt - Bridesmaid&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Valerie is the bride’s friend and roommate from the wonderful days at Wittenberg University.  She may look innocent, but Val is the instigator of many a dorm room dance party. She’ll knock your socks off with deadpan humor and can make a costume out of everything. Literally, anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;John Chambers - Best Man
Sarah Kreuger - Bridesmaid
Danny Chambers - Groomsman
Molly Riffon - Bridesmaid&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Katherine and Michael</name></author><summary type="html">The Wedding</summary></entry></feed>